<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Index xmlns="http://www.tso.co.uk/assets/namespace/gazetteindex" editionCode="L" page="359" pageID="https://www.thegazette.co.uk/id/London/index/year/1922/volume/1/page/359" pagePDF="https://www.thegazette.co.uk/London/index/year/1922/volume/1/page/359" pageRDF="https://www.thegazette.co.uk/London/index/year/1922/volume/1/page/359?view=linked-data" type="index" volume="1" year="1922">
  <ItemGroup>
    <MainItem>
      <Key>Ludlow</Key>
      <Forenames>Hewitt</Forenames>
      <Text>, Group Capt. Edgar Rainey, C.M.G., D.S.O., M.C., A.D.C. (apptd. Air Secretary to Secretary of State for Air and rel. appt. of Deputy Director of Training, Air Ministry) McCrindle, Fit. Lt. John Ronald, O.B.E., M.C. (placed on h.p. Scale B.) (since resd.) ... Macgillivray, Cadet Cyril William Thompson (Hon. 2nd Lt.) .. Rel. hon. commn. on joining T.A McKay, Hon. 2nd Lt. Charles Stephen (rel. hon. commn. on joining T.A.) Mackay, Fit. Cadet Malcolm Bruce (granted permanent commn. as Pilot Otfr.) , ... McKechnie, Flying Offr. Hector George (resigns permanent coinmn.) ... Mackenzie, Mrs. Louisa Learmouth (copfd. in appt. as Staff Nurse) Maclaren, Duncan (corr.) Macpherson, Lt. (Lt., Black Watch) Roderick Charles (rel. temp. R.A.F. commn. on return to 7 Army duty) _ Mac Vicar, Miss Mary Anne (confd. in appt. as Staff Nurse) ... Maffey, Lt. Ernest (rel. temp, commn. on ceasing to be empla. and retains rank of Lt.) ... Mallet, Capt. (Army Dental Corps) Henry flemsted (granted temp, commn. as Fit. Lt while attd. for duty with R.A.F. ... Mangles, Fit. Cadet Roland Arthur Ross (granted permanent commn. as Pilot Offr.) Marler, Eric (granted short service commn. as Pilot Offr. on prob.) Martin, Cadet Percy Leonard (hon. 2nd Lt.) Rel. hon. commn. ... ... Martindale, Stanley Arthur (granted short service comnm. as Flying Offr.) Mason, Cyril Arthur (granted short service commn. as Flying Offr.)</Text>
      <PageNumber>375</PageNumber>
    </MainItem>
  </ItemGroup>
  <KeyDitto>___ ___ ___</KeyDitto>
  <KeyDitto>___ ___</KeyDitto>
  <ItemGroup>
    <MainItem>
      <Key>
        <KeyDitto>___ ___</KeyDitto>
      </Key>
      <Forenames>Robeit Lester</Forenames>
      <Text>(granted short serv commn. as Pilot Offr. on prob.) Penny, Lt. Marcus Gfanfield (granted temp, commn. as Flying Offr. on seedg. for</Text>
      <PageNumber>4</PageNumber>
    </MainItem>
  </ItemGroup>
  <ItemGroup>
    <MainItem>
      <Key>Pliaroah-Band</Key>
      <Forenames>Flying Offr</Forenames>
      <Text>. Lawrence Claud (resigns short serv. commn. and retains rank of Lt.) Phillips, John Sever (granted short serv. commn. as Pilot Offr. on prob.) Pigott, 2nd Lt. George Godfrey Caledon (granted short serv. commn. 'as Flying Offr. on prob.) ... ... Polden, Flying Offr. Charles Joseph (granted permanent 172 commn. and trd. to Stores Branch.) 23305 Not in Gaz. 12th Sept</Text>
      <PageNumber>1919</PageNumber>
    </MainItem>
    <SubItem>
      <Text>cancelled) Ranken, WingCdr. Francis, O.B.E. (placed on half pay, scale B.)</Text>
      <PageNumber>964</PageNumber>
    </SubItem>
    <SubItem>
      <Text>Ransfoid, Alan Carpmael (granted temp, commn. as Fit. Lt.)</Text>
      <PageNumber>1725</PageNumber>
    </SubItem>
  </ItemGroup>
</Index>

